kasabian.co.uk 2012-12-06

# PRIVACY POLICY

                                                                                      PRIVACY POLICY
Last updated 10 February 2009
WHO WE ARE
This privacy policy explains the data protection practices of Sony Music Entertainment. Sony Music Entertainment UK
Limited is a company registered in England with company number 01471066 and whose registered address is 9 Derry
Street, London, W8 5HY. Where we refer to "Sony Music Entertainment", "us" or "we", we mean Sony Music
Entertainment UK Limited (or any Sony Music Entertainment entity using your data in accordance with this policy). We are
committed to protecting and respecting your privacy and the following sets out the basis on which any personal data we
collect from you, or that you provide to us, will be processed. Please read the text carefully to understand our views and
practices regarding your personal data and how we will treat it.
A SPECIAL NOTE TO CHILDREN UNDER 13 YEARS OF AGE
YOU MUST BE 13 YEARS OF AGE OR OLDER TO REGISTER WITH OUR SITE. PLEASE DO NOT REGISTER IF YOU ARE UNDER 13
YEARS OF AGE.
A SPECIAL NOTE TO PARENTS
Parents should supervise their children's online activities and consider using parental control tools available from online
services and software manufacturers that help provide a child-friendly online environment. These tools can also prevent
children from disclosing online their name, address, and other personal information without parental permission.
HOW WE COLLECT YOUR DATA
(a) From you
We may collect and process personal data relating to you by you providing such personal data by filling in forms on our site
or by you contacting us. This includes, but is not limited to, information provided at the time of registering to use (or
become a member of) our site, subscribing to any services (e.g. newsletters), purchasing downloads, posting material or
requesting further services. (b) By using cookies
In addition, we may use 'cookies' to collect data relating to your general internet usage (see also 'Third Party Cookies'
below). This data may include IP-addresses, browser version, number of visits and similar such data relating to your
navigation of the internet and our site. A 'cookie' is a small text file that is placed on your computer's hard drive. Cookies
help us to improve our site and to deliver a better and more personalised service, for instance by storing information about
your preferences and allowing us to recognise you when you return to our site.
You may refuse to accept cookies by activating settings on your internet browser. However, please note that if you select
such settings you may be unable to access certain parts of our site.
TRANSMISSION OF YOUR DATA VIA THE INTERNET
Unfortunately, the transmission of information via the internet is not completely secure. Any transmission is therefore at
your own risk.
Once we have received your data, we will use strict procedures and security features to try to prevent unauthorised access.
However, we cannot guarantee that any information you submit to us will be free from unauthorized third party intrusion.
Where we have given you (or where you have chosen) a password which enables you to access certain parts of our site,
you are responsible for keeping this password confidential. We ask you not to share the password with anyone.
WHERE YOUR DATA IS KEPT OR TRANSFERRED
The data that we collect may be transferred to, and stored at, a destination outside the European Economic Area ("EEA"),
for instance if any of our servers from time to time are located outside the EEA or if one of our service providers or
suppliers is located in a country outside the EEA or if we share your data (in accordance with the 'With whom we share
your data' section below).
Where any of those destinations are countries that do not have data protection laws as stringent as those to which we are
subject, we will take all steps necessary to ensure that your data is only transferred lawfully out of the EEA, and used in
accordance with this privacy policy.
HOW WE USE YOUR DATA
We use the data collected from our site in the following ways: - to ensure that content from our site is presented in the
most effective manner for you and for your computer.
- to provide you with information, products or services that you have requested from us (or third parties, where
appropriate) or which, based on your musical preferences or use, we feel may interest you.
- to carry out our obligations arising from any contracts entered into between you and us.
- to allow you to participate in interactive features of our service, when you choose to do so.
- to notify you about changes to our service.

WITH WHOM WE SHARE YOUR DATA
Subject to the other terms of this policy, and where appropriate, we may share your personal data with the following:
(a) Group companies and third party service providers
We may share your personal data with our affiliated or group companies worldwide and third party service providers.
(b) Artists
We may share your personal data with those artists (and their management companies) that you have expressed an
interest in, who may then use your data, in accordance with this policy, to keep you updated with information about them.
(c) Other third parties
We may transfer, sell or assign any data, including personally identifiable data, to third parties, only in connection with the
sale, merger, consolidation, change in control, transfer of substantial assets, reorganization or liquidation of Sony Music
Entertainment, or any part of it.
We may share with others, at our discretion, certain aggregate statistical data about purchases and the use of our content,
which data may include demographic data such as the age range and/or geographic location of groups of users. No
personal data (such as names or email addresses) will be identifiable from such statistics.
(d) In special circumstances
We may disclose personal data in special cases when we have reason to believe that disclosing this data is necessary to
identify, contact or bring legal action against someone who may be causing injury to or interference (either intentionally or
unintentionally) with the rights or property of those described above in paragraph (a) or (b). We may also disclose your
personal data when we believe in good faith that the law requires us to do so.
YOUR RIGHT TO OBTAIN, CHANGE OR REMOVE YOUR DATA
You can opt out of receiving any further messages from Sony Music Entertainment or anyone with whom we share your
data (as described above) at any time by following the unsubscribe instructions in any message sent to you. If you wish to
unsubscribe from messages we send you, you can also send an email to musicinfo[at]sonymusic.com. You have a right to
access the personal data we hold about you. To obtain a copy of the personal information we hold about you, please write
to us at our registered address provided at the beginning of this privacy policy.
OTHER WEBSITES
Our website may contain links to other websites which are outside our control and are not covered by this privacy policy. If
you access other sites using the links provided, the operators of these sites may collect and process information from you
in a way which is different to how we do so.
THIRD PARTY COOKIES
Some of the advertisements on this site may be generated by third party partners. These third parties may use their own
"cookies" to track how many unique users have seen, or click on, a particular advertisement. These cookies cannot be used
to identify you as an individual, and are used only for statistical purposes or, for example, to provide advertisements that
are more relevant to your preferences. Sony Music Entertainment is not responsible third party cookies, other than
allowing them to be served via our websites. However, we may use statistical information arising from these third party
cookies that is provided to us, if at all, by such third parties to improve the targeting of advertisements to users (see also
'How we collect your data' above).
If you wish to block third party cookies, you can do so in your browser's security settings.
CHANGES TO OUR PRIVACY POLICY
We may modify, alter or otherwise update this privacy policy at any time. We will indicate any changes by updating the
date at the top of the policy. We encourage you to review this policy from time to time.
